Guide to the Anthony Edward Siegman Papers SC1171
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Administrative files
  - JSB Multijurisdictional GP: Notes, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - JSB Workshops, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - JSB PhII RFP, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Stanf Ave Aerial, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - JSB Exhibits, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - SCRL Board Rosters, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Lowell, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Aerial Map, Stanford Area, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - JSB and Roads Cty pre-history, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - SCRL Solar, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Jeannie Howard Siegman SCRL Board of Directors Orientation, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - SCRL NLTR Lowell arrives, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Land Use (Various), 1997 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - SCRL Bylaws, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - SA+Trails: City of PA Comments, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - S1 Trail Map, undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Multi J Traffic Gp, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Design, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - MultiJurisdictional Group Roster, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Multi-J Notes, 2005 Dec (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - SU GUP Annual Report, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - JSB/Santa Marie Drainage, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - MTAG Roster, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - JSB: Cast of Characters, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - JSB Phase II: Drainage, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - JSB Crashes, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - MTAG Agendas, Minutes, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - DKS, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - JSB Phase II, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - JSB Trucks, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - JSB History, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Multi JD Tr 60, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Truck Detector, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - JSB History, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Grant Application, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - College Ter., 2004 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - JSB Neighbors, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Nixon mtg, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Petition, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - JSB Photos, undated (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - JSB History, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - JSB Working Gp 98ff Charge, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Stanf Avenue History, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - GUP Trails Poem, undated (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - GUP Annual Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - GUP FAQ, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - GUP DEIR, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - GUP Trails, undated (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - SCRL StanfAve Paw, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Roads -> Sopes re Stanf Ave, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Stanf Ave: Dutton Re Simitian Plan, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Stanford Ave: U-Turns, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - F&P: JSB Original Dest., 1994 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - JSB: DKS, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Unfinished Business, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - MTAG II: COE Carter Coutre Siegman, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - MTAG II: Formation, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - MTAG II: Roster, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - MTG - MTGS, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Pre-MTG: Warm Up, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - MTAG II: Stanford Ave, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Stanford Ave, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - MTAG II Meetings, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - TLC Grant App, undated (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - Roads MTC Grant Applic, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - No Grant - Now What? COE, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - SCRL Housing Task Force, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - SCRL Emer Map EAP's, undated (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - PANDA, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - SCRL Annual, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - SCRL Nom, Bios, Ann Mg, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - PA Citywide School Commute Safety, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - TC Designs to Consider, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - RFP I & II, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Residents Comments, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - JSB Siegman-Loquist, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - JSB Driveway Authorizations, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - JSB Trucking Signage, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - Stanford Ave: Masoud's Plan, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - JSB, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - JSB Subgroup, undated (Box 17, Folder 100)
  - JB Phase 2 Design, undated (Box 17, Folder 101)
  - Trucks: Shopping Ctr, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 102)
  - SCRL XCom, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - SCRL Exceptional $, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 104)
  - SCRL: Frenchman's, undated (Box 17, Folder 105)
  - Munger Fehr and Peers, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 106)
  - Ground Rent, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 107)
  - SCRL Historical Houses, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 108)
  - SCRL: Budget, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 109)
  - SCRL: Comm O'view NLTR, Web, etc, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 110)
  - SCRL Board, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - SCRL XCOM, undated (Box 17, Folder 112)
  - XCOM-L.P.-Orientation, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 113)
  - Zoback/JSB & Gerona, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - SCRL Website Update Traffic, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 115)
  - JSB Trucks (Tuneup), 2005 (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - Survey Retired Lease Holders, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 117)
  - SCRL Finances O'View Christofferson, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 118)
  - Provost's Special Funds, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 119)
  - Leases, undated (Box 17, Folder 120)
  - Foothills PubAccess, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 121)
  - Spectrum, Radio Wireless, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 122)
  - Trails Poem, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 123)
  - SUPES GUP Trails, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 124)
  - Graphs & Images for Lecture on Lazers - Part 1, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Graphs & Images for Lecture on Lazers - Part 2, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Graphs & Images for Lecture on Lazers - Part 3, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Articles, Correspondence, Photos, & Negatives - Lazers, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Lazer Applications I (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Large Photographs - B/W (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Lazer Gyros/ Fiber Gyros - Articles, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Large Projector Images for Lecture on Lazers (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Slides - Lazers (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Slides - Lazers (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Anti Res. Ring (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Beam Quality (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Bell's THM (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Coupled Fiber Array Beams (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - DFT Localization (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Non-normal Modes Talk - SPIE Meeting, San Diego, 2001 Jul (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - ENF/ Non-normal/ Petermanw: Hong Kong (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - ENF: Scattering Matrix Analysis (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - ENF REFS (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - ENF REFS (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - FDML Mode Locking (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - FHT (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - FHT Algorithm (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - FHT: Manuscript For OSA Letters (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - FHT Criteria & Formulas (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Bessel Functions (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - "Gardern Transform" Reprints (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - FHT: LEC's (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - FIber Fourier Optics (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Fiber Lazer Ampl. (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Filamentation (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Small-scale Self-Focusing (Filmentation) (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Filamentation MS (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - FM Fiber Lazers (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Fischer Mode-Locking Analyses (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - FM Lazer Modes (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Gouy (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Hall Effect of Light (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Masers as Heat Engines (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Int. Locking (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - LAM (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Long. Adjoint Coupling (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Lunar Ranging (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Mode Competition (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Nuclear Spin Maser (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Human Masers (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Mode History (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - NMR Reprints (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Solar/ Actinometers (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - ALDA (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Anan'ev (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Annual Faculty Record Supplement (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Bulgaria - Part 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Bulgaria - Part 2 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Yuh Jen Cheng (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - China (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Cho, Yoshio (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Cincinatti/ Ray Graf (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Cincinatti, 1995 Sep (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - International Conference on Lazers & Their Application, 1970 Jun 09-17 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - EE 231 MAT'LS (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - ELBA NATO-ASI (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Taiwan Lazer School (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Fukushima T. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Furumoto, Grant (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Furumoto Final Report (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Furukawa: Admin. (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Furukawa Documents (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Grant Swinger (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Misc. Humboldt Stuff (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Japanese Visitors (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Indirect Cost Study - Part 1 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Indirect Cost Study - Part 2 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Qualifying Exams (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Quebec BQ Workshop (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Research Projects/Ideas (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Resistor Paradox (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Rochester, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Rochester CQ 07 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Rochester (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Rochester (Forbes) Workshop, 1997 Jun (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Russian Contacts (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Russian Contacts (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Russian Contacts (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Lazer Centers (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Russian Contacts: Dresden "Laser Tagung" (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Sabbatical, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Sabbatical - Zurich, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Science Core (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - SCIOPT (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Seguin Seminar (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - "Zodiac" Multi-Channel Excitation & Optical Extraction Geometry for Compact, High Average Power Industrial Lazers (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Seguin Reco. (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Shanghai (Wuxi) Mtg, 1999 Aug (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Spie Short Course on Lazers (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Alexei Sokolov (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Stankov, Krassimir -- Sofia U. (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - International Workshop on Optical Phase Conjugation & Instabilities, 1982 Sep (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Teklicon (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Teklicon/ Lasergenics/ Admin (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Teklicon/ Lasergenics/ Notes (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - TEX (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - TEX to WEB (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Therma - Wave (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Ivan Tomov (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Japan Trip (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Judy (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Kino Fellow Nomination (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Todd Friedman, Kirkland, & Ellis (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Kleiner Perkins (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Korea Trip, 2009 Sep (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Korean Trip (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Korean Visitors (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Kostenbauder (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Laser Book Collection (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Laser History Project (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Laser Book Design (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Bookmaking in TEX (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Laser Book (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Laser Book: China (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Lasers - New Version (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - "Lazers" - Bulgaria (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Revisions (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Book: Errata (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Laser Book (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Leiden Trip (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Leiden Stuff (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Leningrad: "Computers in Education" (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Leningrad (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Leningrad Laser Symposium, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - McMurtry Chair (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Munich Year (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Mitsubishi (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Maiman Party (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Munich (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Paul Mussche (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - NAE (National Academy of Engineering) (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - TRB Transit Report (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - National Academy of Science Annual Meetings & Correspondences (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - NATO RES Workshop (Smolenice) (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - New, G.H.C. (Imperial College) (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - New Focus Patent Case (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - One Ha/ Yan Sun (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - OTL (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Overhead, 1986-1991 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Overhead Memo (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Virtual Source I (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Virtual Source II (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - VRM Res. Refs (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Wavelets (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Waveguide Lasers (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Wavemeter (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Wolf Effect (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Wood's Anomalies (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - X-Ray Lasers (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - R. Trebino (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Shaw, H. John (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Carlsen Thesis (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Spektrometermodell (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Laser Machining (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Iodine Lasers (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Interferometry (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - He-Ne 3.39 µ, He-Xe 3.51 µ (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Laser Plasma Noise (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Stable 6328A Laser Designs (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - He-Ne Lasers II - Mechanism (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - He-Ne Lasers (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - He-Ne Lasers I - Mechanisms (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Harmonic Generation (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Gas Lasers (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Freq-shifted Feedback (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Flashlamp - Simmering, Etc. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Fiber Optics (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - FHT Notes (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Excimer Lasers (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - "Exact Cavity EQNS" (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - EIT (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - 7.2 Dye Lasers (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Dye Lasers (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Ducts (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - The Institute of Optics - Dye Laser Technology, 1978 Oct 30 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Dye Lasers (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Distributed Feedback & Coupled Wave Theory (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Tony Fest (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Trieste Laser School (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Trieste/Rome, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - T-LEG/ T3L (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - UNS Res History (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Emil Warburg Symposium (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Women Faculty (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Women Faculty (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - To Do List (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Lasers: Looking Back 50 Years (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Correspondence
  - A.E. Siegman Correspondence, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - A.E. Siegman Correspondence, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Hobart, 35503 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - A.E. Siegman Correspondence, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - A.E. Siegman Correspondence, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - AES Chron File, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - GL Finances, 1976-1983 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - NAE/NAS, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - GL Data, 1977-1983 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - MRB Correspondence, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence M.R. Beasley L-Z, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence M.R. Beasley A-K, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Subject files
  - Laser Amplitude Fluctuations, 1963-1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Angular Momentum, 1998-2001 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Angular Momentum of Light, 1993-2000 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Anti-Resonant Ring, 1972-2000 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Bell's Inequality, 1978-1988 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Berry's Phase, 1987-1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Bistability, 1983-85 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Bistable Optical Systems, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Bolt Hole Beams, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Bolt Hole Beams (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Bolt Hole Beams, 1995 October (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Bound States (Positive Energy), 1988, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Blackbody Radiation in W-Gs, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Cavity Dumping, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Chaos in Lasers, 1982-1998 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Chaotic Resonators, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Chemical Lasers, 1993 December (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - CHG JOSA A MS Notes, 1994-1997 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - CHG Notes, 1967, 1973, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - CHG Trannys, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Coherent Artifacts, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Coherence Spikes, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Coherent Transients, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Coherence Theory, 1995, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Coherence Collapse, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Laser Cooling, 1999 August (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Cosmetic Lasers, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Dicke Patent, 1958 September 9 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Diffusion-Driven P.D., 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Publications, 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Titles, undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Fast PDs, undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Theory, undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Edge and Gap, undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Results, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - SOS, undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Results, undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Summary, undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Extensions, undated (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Bipolar, undated (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Diode Laser Demo Setup, 1991-1999 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Levenson Experiment, 1989, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Mercury Ion Laser, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Michelson Echelon, 1965 March (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Mode Competition, 1966, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Modulation - Light Modulators, 1987 November (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Monolithic UNS-Resonator Output Coupler, 1994 May (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - "Noise Eaters", 1996 June 24 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Noise Refs, 1986-1993 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Noise Talk, 1957, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Noise Talk, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Noise in Detectors, 1981 June 23 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Noise Theorem, 1963-1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Noise in Oscillators, 1978-1994 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Frequency Fluctuations, 1967-1978, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Sinusoidal Gaussians, 1997 February 12 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Frequency Fluctuations: Theory and Novel Measurement Methods, 1952-1973 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Optical Heterodyne, 1965 June (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Optical Heterodyning, 1966-1977 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Optical Heterodyning, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Parametric Flourescence, 1963, 1967, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Wave Mixing/Grating Effects, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Parametrics, 1964, 1973-1976 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Optical Parametric Amplifiers, 1966-1973 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Optical Parametric Oscillators - Byer, 1973 January (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - "Perfect Mirrors", 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - PCM Res. Chapter, 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Phase Conj. Talk, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Photorefractive Effect, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Photon Statistics, 1977-1988 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Photon Statistics, 1980-1984 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Photoemission Statistics, 1963-1973 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Prony: Reprints, 1968-1978 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Prony Reprints, 1963-1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Wave Mixing and Phase Conjugation - Notes, 1977-1982 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - PSEC Sampling and Switching, 1980-1985 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Quartic Abberation Analysis, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Radiation Trapping, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Rare Earths, 1983 May (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Ray-Pulse, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Ray-Pulse Matrices, 1989-1995 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Rhodopsin: Seminar, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Rhodopsin: Bacteriorbiodopsin, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Rhodopsin: Stanford Results, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Ring Lasers, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Ripples: Reprints, 1982-1999 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Ripples: Seminar, 1982-1986 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Rydberg Atoms, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Saturated Absorption Spectroscopy, 1971-1976 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Scully, 1985-1988 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Short-Cavity Lasers, 1968, 1976-1984 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Speckle, 1963, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Reprints on Spectroscopes and Dispersing Elements, 1954 October (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Spontaneous Emission Lifetime Modification, 1973-1987 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Star Wars, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Subnatural Linewidth Spectros Copy, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Tapered Knife Edge MS, 1996 September (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Email and Articles from Klaus Wittig, 1996 August (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Tapered Slits and Knife Edges, 1994-1996 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Thermal, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Ultrashort Cav. Lasers, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Overhead, 1971-1985 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Overhead Messages, 1991-1994 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Paraxia (Current Stuff), 1996 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Paraxia User Manual, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Paraxia Tech Notes, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Paraxia Software Queries, 1991-1995 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Paraxia, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Patents, 1999-2001 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - PFund Patent: Admin. Stuff, 1994-1998 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - PH.D. Students, 1979-1995 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 1999 December (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - PLM (Precision Laser Machining) - TRW, 2000 May 24 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - PLM Annual - LAX, 2000 May (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - PLM - LAX, 1998 December (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - PLM Proposal, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - PLM - LAX, 1998 April 14 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - PLM Meeting Stanford, 1997 December (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - PLM Excom - Penn State, 1997 October 2 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - PLM Minutes, 1998 April 14 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - PLM - Mountain View, 1995 June 24 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - PLM Excom - Seattle, 1997 April 24 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - PLM BQ, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - ARPA - Advanced Research Projets Agency/PLM, 1995 November/December (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - PLM Seattle, 1997 April 24 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - ARPA/PLM Meeting, 1996 November/December (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - DARPA/PLM Schenectady, 1995 December (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Q-Peak, 2004 February (Box 28, Folder 28)
- History files
  - Hist: Mag. Resonance, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Hist: Maiman, 1960-2010 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Hist: Maiman (Nelson Nonsense), 2010 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Hist: Masers, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Hist: Microwaves, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Hist: Natural Masers, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - OSA History, 1966, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hist: Nutting, 1917, 2000, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Hist: Pake, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - OSA: Kingslake History 1965, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - OSA History Project, 1917, 2005-2008 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Hist: Parametric Flourescence, 1957, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Hist: People (Misc.), 2003, 2004, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Hist: Pre-Laser Laser Phenom, 1955, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Hist: Ramsey, 1960, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Hist: Russian Lasers, 1985, 2002-2009 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Basou from Ionin, undated (Box 4, Folder 25A)
  - Hist: Schawlow, 2003, 2004, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Hist: Snitzer, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Hist: Sorokin, 1979, 1985, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Hist: Special Issue, 1962-2005 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Hist: Silicon Valley, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Hist: Spie Interview, 2008-2010 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - History: Stanford, Chronology, 2000-2007 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Townes, Charles H., 2006, 2007, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Townes Interview, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Hist: Tolman, 1951, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Hist: Townes, 1962, 1983, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Hist: Weber, Joe, 1951-1954, 2008 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Hist: WWII, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Laser Market Surveys, 1966, 1995-2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Laser History Talk, 1916-2006 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Laser History Talk (2), circa 2009 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Laser History Talk (3), circa 2009 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Publications
  - Pubs by Year, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Characteristics of ruby for maser applications W.S.C. Chang and A.E. Siegman, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - The waves on a filamentary electron beam in a transverse-field slow-wave circuit, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 24)